[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "I mean, there must have been a point where you thought you were all going to die, wasn't there?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "there", "must", "have", "been", "a", "point", "where", "you", "thought", "you", "were", "all", "going", "to", "die", ",", "was", "n't", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Kyung, what's the latest from where you are?", "question_tokens": ["Kyung", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "latest", "from", "where", "you", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "From where we are, we're starting to continue to see more and more damage, Piers, as we get closer and closer.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "where", "we", "are", ",", "we", "'re", "starting", "to", "continue", "to", "see", "more", "and", "more", "damage", ",", "Piers", ",", "as", "we", "get", "closer", "and", "closer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Do you have any sense from what you're seeing, from what you're hearing about any kind of death toll?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "sense", "from", "what", "you", "'re", "seeing", ",", "from", "what", "you", "'re", "hearing", "about", "any", "kind", "of", "death", "toll", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "It's really hard to imagine.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "really", "hard", "to", "imagine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Can you describe to me what is actually going on?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "describe", "to", "me", "what", "is", "actually", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Morgan"]}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Could you please start by telling me what your understanding of the scale of this disaster is in terms of people who've been wounded, possibly killed?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "please", "start", "by", "telling", "me", "what", "your", "understanding", "of", "the", "scale", "of", "this", "disaster", "is", "in", "terms", "of", "people", "who", "'ve", "been", "wounded", ",", "possibly", "killed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Thank you very much, Mr. Morgan, for giving me this opportunity.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "very", "much", ",", "Mr.", "Morgan", ",", "for", "giving", "me", "this", "opportunity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "I mean are you fearing here -- that you may be seeing a toll much, much higher?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "are", "you", "fearing", "here", "--", "that", "you", "may", "be", "seeing", "a", "toll", "much", ",", "much", "higher", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "As what I said is the figure that we have identified up to now.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "what", "I", "said", "is", "the", "figure", "that", "we", "have", "identified", "up", "to", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Can you tell me what the latest is in relation to those plants?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "tell", "me", "what", "the", "latest", "is", "in", "relation", "to", "those", "plants", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "DT", "JJS", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Yes, we are talking about the Fukushima nuclear power plant, and there are two sites.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "are", "talking", "about", "the", "Fukushima", "nuclear", "power", "plant", ",", "and", "there", "are", "two", "sites", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "I mean, is it possible we could see a meltdown of one of these plants?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "it", "possible", "we", "could", "see", "a", "meltdown", "of", "one", "of", "these", "plants", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "I am sorry, I'm not in a position to speculate on that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "sorry", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "in", "a", "position", "to", "speculate", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "Ken, can I start with you and just ask you what you think is going on from an expert point of view here?", "question_tokens": ["Ken", ",", "can", "I", "start", "with", "you", "and", "just", "ask", "you", "what", "you", "think", "is", "going", "on", "from", "an", "expert", "point", "of", "view", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Well, it's not the answer you want to hear, but I would say that statistical analysis would have a hard time finding a pattern here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "the", "answer", "you", "want", "to", "hear", ",", "but", "I", "would", "say", "that", "statistical", "analysis", "would", "have", "a", "hard", "time", "finding", "a", "pattern", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Is this actually how it sounds?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "actually", "how", "it", "sounds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ken"], "LOCATION": ["Sendai"]}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "What do you think is happening here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "happening", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Well, I think Ken has a good point that if you looked at the geological history of this area, there's been repeated tsunamis generated in the Sendai area.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "Ken", "has", "a", "good", "point", "that", "if", "you", "looked", "at", "the", "geological", "history", "of", "this", "area", ",", "there", "'s", "been", "repeated", "tsunamis", "generated", "in", "the", "Sendai", "area", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Is this complete nonsense, or is there any kind of credence to that theory?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "complete", "nonsense", ",", "or", "is", "there", "any", "kind", "of", "credence", "to", "that", "theory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "It's complete nonsense, but I don't like saying it's nonsense without defending why it is so.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "complete", "nonsense", ",", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "like", "saying", "it", "'s", "nonsense", "without", "defending", "why", "it", "is", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Is this one of the inevitable repercussions of an earthquake that size?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "one", "of", "the", "inevitable", "repercussions", "of", "an", "earthquake", "that", "size", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Well, aftershocks do follow some general patterns and can be statistically analyzed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "aftershocks", "do", "follow", "some", "general", "patterns", "and", "can", "be", "statistically", "analyzed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "What possible comfort can you offer them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "possible", "comfort", "can", "you", "offer", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "ERKUS: Well, there's several things.", "answer_tokens": ["ERKUS", ":", "Well", ",", "there", "'s", "several", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Red Cross"]}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Given we've experienced this before there, what do you think is the most sensible and immediate thing that should be done to help the people in Japan?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "we", "'ve", "experienced", "this", "before", "there", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "is", "the", "most", "sensible", "and", "immediate", "thing", "that", "should", "be", "done", "to", "help", "the", "people", "in", "Japan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "EX", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I think people should be texting to the Red Cross.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "people", "should", "be", "texting", "to", "the", "Red", "Cross", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Matthew, if I may start with you, what is your understanding of the latest situation at the Fukushima plant?", "question_tokens": ["Matthew", ",", "if", "I", "may", "start", "with", "you", ",", "what", "is", "your", "understanding", "of", "the", "latest", "situation", "at", "the", "Fukushima", "plant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "They -- when you shut down a nuclear plant, you're continuing to produce heat.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "--", "when", "you", "shut", "down", "a", "nuclear", "plant", ",", "you", "'re", "continuing", "to", "produce", "heat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Fukushima"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "What is the hour-by-hour time scale that we could be looking at before there's some sort of inevitable meltdown?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "hour-by-hour", "time", "scale", "that", "we", "could", "be", "looking", "at", "before", "there", "'s", "some", "sort", "of", "inevitable", "meltdown", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "At this point, a meltdown is not inevitable.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "this", "point", ",", "a", "meltdown", "is", "not", "inevitable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "How serious do you think this one is in Japan?", "question_tokens": ["How", "serious", "do", "you", "think", "this", "one", "is", "in", "Japan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "CD", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Well, actually there haven't been very many situations of this degree of seriousness.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", "there", "have", "n't", "been", "very", "many", "situations", "of", "this", "degree", "of", "seriousness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Asia", "United States"]}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "CC", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "And what does it mean for nuclear plants in America, for example, if a similar thing was to happen here?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "does", "it", "mean", "for", "nuclear", "plants", "in", "America", ",", "for", "example", ",", "if", "a", "similar", "thing", "was", "to", "happen", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "There's the beginning of renaissance in nuclear construction all over Asia and, to some extent, in the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "the", "beginning", "of", "renaissance", "in", "nuclear", "construction", "all", "over", "Asia", "and", ",", "to", "some", "extent", ",", "in", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Japan", "Los Angeles", "United States"]}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "And if so, are we prepared to deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "so", ",", "are", "we", "prepared", "to", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "First of all, Piers, our hearts and prayers are with the people of Japan, and the -- the Japanese American community that lives here in Los Angeles, the largest in the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "Piers", ",", "our", "hearts", "and", "prayers", "are", "with", "the", "people", "of", "Japan", ",", "and", "the", "--", "the", "Japanese", "American", "community", "that", "lives", "here", "in", "Los", "Angeles", ",", "the", "largest", "in", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "How fast can these tsunamis strike, can these quakes strike?", "question_tokens": ["How", "fast", "can", "these", "tsunamis", "strike", ",", "can", "these", "quakes", "strike", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Well, I'm not an expert on that, but I can tell you the following: I got in real-time on my Blackberry.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "an", "expert", "on", "that", ",", "but", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "the", "following", ":", "I", "got", "in", "real-time", "on", "my", "Blackberry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Is that just crass stupidity, in your view?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "just", "crass", "stupidity", ",", "in", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Have you in your lifetime seen anything quite like what we witnessed in Japan in the last 24 hours?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "in", "your", "lifetime", "seen", "anything", "quite", "like", "what", "we", "witnessed", "in", "Japan", "in", "the", "last", "24", "hours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "No, definitely not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "definitely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "What is the ring of fire and what does it mean now going forward?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "ring", "of", "fire", "and", "what", "does", "it", "mean", "now", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Incredibly active zone, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Incredibly", "active", "zone", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110311pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Is it now completely unpredictable?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "now", "completely", "unpredictable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Piers, if I could forecast the weather for the rest of the year, I would do it right now, go home and call it a day.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "if", "I", "could", "forecast", "the", "weather", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "year", ",", "I", "would", "do", "it", "right", "now", ",", "go", "home", "and", "call", "it", "a", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]